(Sheldon:)but the smell of burning books
(Sheldon:)reminds me of church picnics
in East Texas.
(Howard:)What's this?
(Sheldon:)That's just a doodle of
a hyperelliptic Riemann surface.
(Leonard:)Oh, yeah. Wasn't that the basis
of your postdoc fellowship?
(Sheldon:)It was.
(Sheldon:)This seemed so elegant
at the time,
(Sheldon:)but now I realize I was just
a simple country boy,
(Sheldon:)seduced by a big city theory
(Sheldon:)with variables
in all the right places.
(Raj:)-It's going to be OK.
-I know.
(Sheldon:)As hard as this is,
I have to move on.
(Sheldon:)I can't keep postulating
multidimensional entities
(Sheldon:)and get nothing in return.
(Sheldon:)I have needs, too.
(Howard:)So, you and Emily
still together?
(Howard:)I spoke to Bernadette.
She's free tomorrow night.
OK, great.